3 Times the Laughs. 3 Times the Stupid. 3 Times the Pain.
Jackass 3D is a comedy, documentary, action film directed by Jeff Tremaine.
Johnny Knoxville, Bam Margera, Steve-O, Wee Man and the rest of their fearless and
foolhardy friends take part in another round of outrageous pranks and stunts.
In addition to standing in the path of a charging bull, launching themselves into the air and crashing through various objects,
the guys perform in segments such as "Sweatsuit Cocktail," "Beehive Tetherball" and "Lamborghini Tooth Pull."
Self, played by Johnny Knoxville.
Self, played by Bam Margera.
Self, played by Ryan Dunn.
Self, played by Steve-O.
Self, played by Chris Pontius.
Self, played by Jason 'Wee Man' Acuña.
Jackass 3D (known as Jackass 3 on home media) is a 2010 American
3D reality comedy film directed by Jeff Tremaine.
It is the third installment in the Jackass film series, and
the sequel to Jackass Number Two (2006).
The film stars the regular Jackass cast of  Johnny Knoxville, Bam Margera, Ryan Dunn, Steve-O,
"Danger Ehren" McGhehey, Dave England, Preston Lacy, Wee Man, and Chris Pontius.
This is the last Jackass film to feature Dunn before his death in 2011 and Margera as a primary
cast member before his departure in 2020 (Margera is briefly in Jackass Forever).
It is also the last Jackass film to feature a guest
appearance by Rip Taylor, who died in October 2019.
The film was theatrically released in the United States in the 3D format on October 15, 2010, by
Paramount Pictures, marking the tenth anniversary of the Jackass television series.
It received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film grossed $171.7 million worldwide against a
production budget of $20 million.
A sequel, titled Jackass Forever, was released 12 years
later on February 4, 2022, to positive reviews.
Leftover film footage scenes was incorporated as an extended length feature
released as Jackass 3.5, on DVD and Blu-ray on June 14, 2011.
The film explores themes of pain, stunt, stuntman,
stupidity, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted.